Cole, David L. Papers 5588
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Company Exhibits. Opinions and orders of the Board.
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, case notes, wage proposals, etc.
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  Includes correspondence, statement of the committee, records of the Southern Textile Commission.
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  Includes hearing records; correspondence; and a petition for the establishment of job classifications submitted to the Board by the Textile Directive Steering Committee and the TWUA.
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  Includes schedule of rates approved by Southern Textile Commission; Commission decisions; correspondence.
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Joint petition to the Northern Textile Commission by the Textile Directive Steering Committee vs. the TWUA, CIO; press releases; list of Northern mills cited to the War Labor Board; memoranda from the Office of Economic Stabilization; related newspaper articles
- National War Labor Board. Northern Textile Commission., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  Includes statement of policy; press relations announcing the creation of the Textile Commissions; related newspaper articles; case records form the Southern Textile Commissions.
- Steel Panel. Summaries of cases., 1944 (Box 39, Folder 1-7)
  Steel Panel. Summaries of cases. Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, et al., vs. USA. 1944.
- Related materials., 1944 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, "The Cost of Living Index of the Bureau of Labor Statistics"; Journal of the American Statistical Association, "Appraisal of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics Cost of Living Index."
- Related materials., 1936-1943 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  "Cost of Living" by George Meany and R. J. Thomas; "Steel Profits 1936-1943" by USA; article by Journal of the American Statistical Association; "A Critical Analysis of the Meany-Thomas Report on the Cost of Living," National Industrial Conference Board, Inc.
- Meat Packing Report. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  Records of cases between Swift and Co., Armour and Co., Wilson and Co., Cudahy Packing Co., vs. United Packinghouse Workers. of America. CIO.
- Office of War Information, War Production Board. (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  Press releases; hearing notes on Wright Aeronautical Corporation; includes policy statements
- Information on wage rates. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  Correspondence; press releases concerning wage rates; "Official Interpretive Bulletin Relating to Christmas and Year-End Bonus Payments in 1943.
- Information on wage rates. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; press releases; lists of approvable wage rates in the textile industry.
- Information on wage rates. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  Approvable salary rates for department stores, New York City, Metal Trades Draftsmen and Designers, Tool Designers, Flock and Lacquer Printing Employees, Textile Industry, job descriptions and approvable rates of pay in the Metal Trade Industry.
- Information on wage rates. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  Memo on wage brackets in the textile industry, rayon and silk dyeing, printing and finishing, folding paper box, industry, cleaning and dyeing industry, ice manufacturing occupations, service restaurants; "Wage Stabilization General Orders and Interpretation."
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Notes on case hearings; letters and history on case between USA and U.S. Steel Corp.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  Cole's notes on overall summary of Panel findings, copies of unions requests and costs to company.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Exhibits of Universal-Cyclops Steel Corp.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Exhibits from Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corp., et al., vs. USA.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  Exhibits from Sheffield Steel of Texas and USA, Carnegie Steel vs. USA, Index of Exhibits.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Exhibits. Statement of Granite City Steel Company, digest of argument and evidence presented by the United Steel Workers of America; statement on behalf of Andrews Steel Co.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  Statement on behalf of Colorado Fuel and Iron Corp., Company's Brief Supplementing General Presentations of Steel Case Research Committee.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  Statement of the American Rolling Mill Co.; statement on behalf of Follansbee Steel Corp.
- Steel Panel. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Statement on behalf of Reeves Steel and Manufacturing Co.; statement and brief submitted by Mercer Tube and Manufacturing Co.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Briefs involving case between USA and United States Steel Corp., et al. Pamphlet on steel profits 1936 through 1943; pamphlet on earnings and hours in the Iron and Steel Industry, April 1939; "Cost of Living" by George Meany and R. J. Thomas.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  "Pertinent Documents Relating to the Proceedings of Hearings in the matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corp., et al. and United Steel Workers of America"; "Pertinent Documents Relating to the National Economic Stabilization Program, Statement of T. F. Patton.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  Statement of C. A. McLain in Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corp. and USA; statement of Dr. Jules Backman and Dr. Donald G. Cowan in same.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  elated documents. "The Cost of Living of the Bureau of Labor Statistics"; article from Journal of the American Statistical Association.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  "Statement of F. R. Brugler on Corporate Profits and H. W. Boal and John C. Gall, and Bradford B. Smith, all in the matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, et al., and United Steel Workers of America."
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  Statement of Endeis M. Voorhees, Roswell Magill, F. M. Gillies, Kemp G. Fuller in matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, et al., vs. USA.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  Statement of Nicholas Unkovic, Lawrence E. Riddle, Roger Blough, John G. Ketterer, Andrew Court in the matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, et al., vs. USA.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Statements of Frederick Knight, T. F. Patton, D. K. McKamy and John V. Van Sickle, Ernest Ballard in the matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel vs. USA.
- Steel Panel. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  "Statements of Seward H. French, Jr., John G. Ketterer, C. A. McLain and John A. Stephens, General Company Statement in reply to the Rebuttal Presentation of the Union in the matter of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, et al., and United Steel Workers of America."
- Steel Panel. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Statements of Dr. Jules Backman and David S. Roswell; related articles from Bureau of Labor Statistics.
- Steel Panel. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Includes correspondence concerning Steel Panel and Textile Commissions; press releases; transcript of press conference of William H. Davis, Chairman of War Labor Board, held September 15, 1944; addresses of regional Board members.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 3)
  Manual of Board Wage Policies; Memorandum from Theodore Kheel on incentive bonus and absentee bonus.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Includes general correspondence; instructional memoranda to staff; information bulletins; case notes on Public Service Coordinated Transport and Public Service Interstate Company and the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Recommendation of the panel in Remington Rand, Inc., vs. International Association of Machinists, Public Service Coordinated Transport and Public Service Interstate Transportation Co. and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America; Manual of Instruction for Parties in Dispute Cases before the National War Labor Board; Manual of Instructions for Panel Members and Hearing Officers, Statement of Policy Concerning Review of Arbitration Awards.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 6)
  Minutes of meeting; instructional memos; interpretive orders; correspondence; press releases; case opinions
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 7)
  Includes cases heard by the Second Region: Babcock and Wilcox vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE); R. B. Davis Co. vs. IC of CW, Local 21503, AFL; Random House, Inc. vs. United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Artists vs. Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild. Records of these cases include industry dissents and labor dissents. Also includes correspondence, application for wage increases and bonuses; and instructional memos to Regional Boards.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 43, Folder 8)
  Includes information on Region II of the Board. Correspondence, case opinions, applications for wage increases, opinion on absentee bonus plans, and summary of Board's experience in cases involving check-off.
- War Labor Board Second Region, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence concerning cases, wage applications, opinions on Absentee Bonus Plan; minutes of July 1943; meetings of Second Region.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Includes opinions on cases heard by the Second Region, correspondence concerning cases, official report of proceeding in matter of Loose-Wiles Biscuit Co. vs. United Cracker Workers of Greater New York, Local 25, CIO; opinion and recommendation of the panel in the matter of Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. American Communications Association, CIO.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 3)
  Includes notes of cases considered; agenda of Region II meetings; instructional memorandum, memoranda on New York State Electric and Gas Corporations.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Includes notes of cases considered by Region II; memoranda to Board members; Division Report on Republic Steel; statement by Philip Murray of the USA.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
  Includes notes of cases considered by Region II.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 8)
  Milk Panel. Includes notes of hearing heard by Board.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 9)
  Pamphlet on War Labor Board, "What it is ... How it operates"; appeal for wage increases by USA; Union's request for shift differentials; Union's request for holidays; Memoranda to Board on approvable wage rates in the textile industry.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 10)
  Press releases; General Orders; "Procedure Relative to Possible Violation of the Wage and Salary Stabilization Program"; records of hourly earnings in various industries; memorandum to Board on wage brackets in the textile industry.
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 11)
  Addresses of Regional Board members; pamphlet on application of the "Little Steel" formula, amended wage and salary regulations of Office of Economic Stabilization; "Method for the Determination of Wage Adjustment for Employees Working on a Commission Basis"; Executive Order regarding regulations relating to overtime wage compensation; press releases; wage rates for apparel trades; "Jurisdiction and Procedure of the Regional War Labor Boards"; "Wage Incentive Plans."
- War Labor Board Second Region (Box 44, Folder 12)
  War Production Board. Notes on incentive plan for non-incentive workers of the Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. Also includes Official Plan Book of the War Production Board.
- White House Conference on National Economic Issues, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  Correspondence, agenda, summary, notes. 1962.
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 45, Folder All)
  Proceedings, Volumes 1-15, 1948. (Akron and Barberton Belt Railroad Co. vs. certain of their employees represented by the sixteen cooperative Railway Labor Organizations).
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46.1, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46.2, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46.3, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46.4, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 46.5, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 47, Folder All)
  Carriers Exhibits, #1-8.
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 48, Folder All)
  Carriers Exhibits, #9-38.
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 49, Folder All)
  Employees Exhibits, #1-9.
- Emergency Board #66., 1948 (Box 50, Folder All)
  Employee Exhibits, #1-14.
- Emergency Board #73., 1949 (Box 51, Folder All)
  Dispute between the Railway Express Agency and certain of its employees represented by the Brotherhood of Railway Clerks. Transcripts of Proceedings, 1949. Issue: Contract negotiations
- Emergency Board #73., 1949 (Box 52, Folder All)
  Employees Exhibits, #1-23.
- Emergency Board #73., 1949 (Box 53, Folder All)
  Carriers Exhibits, #1-14.
- Emergency Board #94., 1951 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  American Airlines vs. Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA), Report, 1951. Issue: Contract negotiations.
- Emergency Board #94., 1951 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  Carriers Exhibits, #1-29.
- Emergency Board #94., 1951 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  Employees Exhibits, #1-13.
- Emergency Board #94., 1951 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  Employees Exhibits, #14-36.
- Emergency Board #94., 1951 (Box 56, Folder All)
  Employees Exhibits, #37-71.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  Seventeen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations vs. Designated Railroads, 1951-52. Issue: Union security.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  Related papers.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, 1951-52.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  Letters and documents of comment.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  General documents and correspondence.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  Report to the President.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  Railway Labor Act Amendments.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  Carriers' and Employer's Briefs.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  Miscellaneous documents.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  Carriers Exhibits.
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 60, Folder All)
- Emergency Board #98., 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder All)
  Employees Exhibits.
- Emergency Board #120., 1958 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Eastern Airlines vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1958. Issue: Crew size; rates of pay; vacations and vacation pay.
- Emergency Board #121., 1958 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  Eastern Airlines vs. ALPA, 1958. Issue: Crew size; rates of pay; retirement plan.
- Emergency Board #123., 1958 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  Trans World Airway vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1958. Issue: Elimination of jobs.
- Afro-American Publishing Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  4/10/50. Issue: Rates of pay
- Airlift International, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Assn., 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Issues: seniority; bidding; scheduling; bumping
- Airlift International, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Assn., 1968 (Box 64, Folder All)
  Issue: merger; seniority
- Alexander Smith & Sons, A & M Karagheusian, & Bigelow -Sanford vs. Textile Workers. Union of America, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
  5/7/52. Issue: arbitrability - rates of pay
- Allied Restaurant and Entertainment Industry vs. Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks and Assistants of NY, Local 89, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 6-8)
  11/46. Issues: Rates of pay; workweek; vacations; holidays & holiday pay; sick leave & sick pay (Includes transcripts)
- TWUA Reply Brief: Carpet Case, Text; News clipping (Box 65.1, Folder 1)
- TWUA - Research and "Brief on Behalf of Three Carpet Companies: Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Co., Inc.; A. & M. Karagheusian, Inc.; Alexander Smith Inc., 1952; Text (Box 65.1, Folder 2)
- TWUA - Collective Bargaining information and agreement, Text (Box 65.1, Folder 3)
- A & M Karagheusian, Inc. - Wage Reopening, 1952; Text (Box 65.1, Folder 4)
- TWUA & Bigelow - Sanford: This award taken from reg. file, 1951; Text (Box 65.1, Folder 5)
- Alexander Smith & Sons Carpet Co. - TWUA: 1949 -- Hearing Notes, Text (Box 65.1, Folder 6)
- Carpets: Wage Reopening -- Alexander Smith & Sons Carpet Company; Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company; A & M Karagheusian, Inc., 1952; Text (Box 65.1, Folder 7)
- Aloha Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Assn., 1971 (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
  11/23/71. Issues: Reduction in fare; crew size (includes exhibits)
- Aloha Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Assn., 1971 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  11/23/71. Issues: Reduction in fare; crew size; equipment list
- American Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes. Issues: Rates of pay; mileage limits
- American Airlines vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 2-4)
  4/30/54. Exhibits. Issues: Rates of pay; mileage limits
- American Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes re working conditions; hours of work
- American Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 2-3)
  Hearing notes re holiday pay, mileage, rates of pay
- American Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  1/17/75. Exhibits, Interim Award
- American Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  1/17/55. Issue: Hours (shift/scheduling)
- American Jewish Congress vs. Social Service Employees Union, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  Hearing notes re dismissal
- American Steel Foundries vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  9/44. Transcripts
- American Weekly, Division of Hearst Publishing Co. vs. N.Y. Newspaper Guild, Local 3 of American Newspaper Guild, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  3/50. No Award, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of pay
- Atlantic City Transportation vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, 1947 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  Hearing notes re pensions, vacations, rates of pay
- Atlantic City Transportation vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  1/21/48. Issues: Pension benefits; sick & accident benefits; vacation time; lunch periods; holiday pay & holiday work; severance pay; rates of pay; seniority
- American Steel Foundries, Text (Box 68.1, Folder 1)
- American Weekly, Div. of; Hearst Publishing Co. Inc. and Newspaper Guild, 1950; Text (Box 68.1, Folder 2)
- Atlantic City Transportation: Amalgamated Assn. of Street, Electrical Hearing Notes, 1947; Text (Box 68.1, Folder 3)
- Ashland Corp.: Textile Union -- (Complete notes on this case are filed under 'Textile Committee', box 170), Text (Box 68.1, Folder 4)
- Atlantic City Transportation Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
  No award, Exhibits. Issues: Union security; working conditions, rates of pay
- Atlantic City Transportation Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  1/21/48. Transcript
- Bakelite Corporation vs. unidentified, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes re discharge
- Bassick Co. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  Hearing notes re reinstatement with back pay
- Bates Manufacturing Co. vs. Continental (Box 70, Folder 4)
  Notes filed under Textile Committee - Box 170
- Bigelow-Sanford vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Hearing notes re bumping
- Bloomingdale Bros. Inc. vs. United Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Employees of America, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  8/27/48. Issues: Rates of pay; job progressions, medical insurance, night differential; skilled crafts
- Bobbie Brooks, Inc. vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1964-1977 (Box 71, Folder All)
  Notes and correspondence re pending cases
- Bobbie Brooks, Inc. vs. ILGWU, 1965-1975 (Box 72, Folder All)
  Notes, correspondence, decisions by other arbitrators, a few Cole decisions
- Bobbie Brooks, Inc. vs. ILGWU, 1965-1975 (Box 73, Folder All)
- Borden Milk vs. unidentified, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes re overtime pay
- Botany vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1945-1946 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Braniff Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  Hearing notes re seniority - recall
- Bronx Home News Publishing Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, 1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Building Material Industry of NYC vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 282, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 5-6)
  2/13/54. Hearing notes. Issues: Contract terms - extension; modification; revision of terms of agreements
- Butler Bros. vs. United Steelworkers of America, (Iron Ore Panel of N.W.L.B., Cole, Chmn.), 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
  Issues: Wage adjustments; fringe benefits; insurance; check-off
- Carson Newton Co. vs. UE, Local 437, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  4/20/48. Hearing notes re discharge
- Celeanese Corp. of America vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local l874, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  3/48. Issues: Rates of pay-in-equalities; workload. Transcript
- Celeanese Corp. of America vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local l874, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  Transcripts
- Chicago Pneumatic Tool vs. IAM, Local 1170, 1942 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  11/l7/42. Issue: Rates of pay. Hearing notes
- Coca Cola Bottling Co. vs. unidentified, 1945-1947 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Hearing notes re layoff, veteran standards, working conditions
- Colonial Print vs. unidentified, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  Hearing notes re discharge case
- Columbia Broadcasting System vs. United Office and Professional Workers of America, Radio Guild, Local 50, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  8/47. Issue: Vacations. Exhibits
- Con Edison vs. International. Union of Operating Engineers, Local 137 & IBEW, Local 501, 1970-1971 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  Issues: Work assignment; production plans
- Coty, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 815, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  11/56. Hearing notes re rates of pay
- County Gas Co. vs. Utility Company Workers Association, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  4/22/48. Hearing notes re wages, welfare plan, group insurance
- Cudahy Packing Co. vs. United Paperworkers of America, Local 116, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  8/3/48. Hearing notes re vacations
- Daily News vs. American Newspaper Guild, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  11/25/47. Hearing notes re sick leave, wage structure
- Dellwood Dairy vs. Local 338, unidentified union, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  3/23/44. Hearing notes re job posting
- DuMont Labs, Inc. vs. IUE, District 4, 1954-1957 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  Hearing notes re discharge, absenteeism. Transcript of a meeting, correspondence, tape of a meeting
- Duplan Corp. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  3/13/47. Hearing notes re rates of pay, equipment
- Dyers and Printers Pension Fund vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  4/49. Correspondence
- Fabrain Textile Corp. vs. unidentified, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  11/26/46. Hearing notes re discharge
- Fairchild Hiller Corp. vs. IAM, Local 1987, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  12/15/66. Issues: Severance pay, trust fund
- Fairchild Instrument Corp. vs. UE, Local 1217, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  10/4/45. Hearing notes re suspension, rates of pay
- Farrand Optical Co. vs. IUE, Local 475, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  6/24/52. Hearing notes re protests number of arbitrability issues.